Yerdaulet Shapagatov

+1 323 522 5563 Astana, Kazakhstan yershapa@gmail.com Portfolio

Objective

I am a graduate student of Computer Science at Nazarbayev University. I enjoy coding and problem solving, and always strive to give my best to any work I undertake. My bachelor's degree allowed me to gain experience in technologies such as C/C++, C#, Java, Python, and Assembly. I have 5 years of professional experience, which helped me to strengthen my skills in .Net framework, MFC, Delphi, Spring Boot, Hibernate, PineScript, NinjaScript and MQL (MetaQuotes Language). My passion lies in developing complex applications that can solve real-world problems and impact millions of users.

Skills & Abilities

- Languages: C/C++, C#, Java, Python, PineScript, NinjaScript, MQL, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, HTML/CSS, Bash
- Databases: MySQL, SQLite, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis
- Frameworks: .NET, Spring Boot, Hibernate, React/Redux, Next, Vue, Node, Nest, Django, Laravel, Codelgniter, Zend, CakePHP, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS
- Tools & Technologies: Git, Docker, AWS, GCP, Heroku, JIRA

Experience

Jun 2023 – Current

Software Engineer, Guru.com

- Developed and customized Trading Indicators & Strategies for TradingView
- Converted PineScript to NinjaScript, MQL5
- Managed .Net & Vue.js project Frontend and Backend

Skills: C#, JavaScript, PineScript, NinjaScript, MQL5, .Net, Azure, SQL

Dec 2022 - May 2023

Full-Stack Developer, Upwork.com

- Collaborated with a diverse range of clients on Upwork.com to provide fullstack development services for their web applications.
- Designed, developed, and implemented responsive and user-friendly web applications using JS frameworks, and UX/UI on both the front-end and back-end.
- Actively communicated with clients to provide progress updates, address concerns, and ensure project alignment.
- Implemented efficient database structures, optimized query performance, and ensured data integrity.
- Developed and consumed RESTful APIs to integrate third-party services and enhance application functionality.

- Conducted thorough testing, debugging, and troubleshooting to deliver high quality, bug-free code.
- Utilized version control systems, such as Git, for code management and collaboration with clients.
- Maintained documentation, including project specifications, technical guides, and user manuals.

Skills: React/Redux, Next, Vue, Node, Nest, Spring Boot, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

July 2019 – Nov 2022

Software Developer, TELUS International

- Contributed to the development and maintenance of software applications for UEFI firmware.
- Participated in the full software development lifecycle, including requirements gathering, design, coding, testing, and debugging.
- Actively participated in code reviews, providing and receiving constructive feedback to improve code quality.
- Gained expertise in C, Assembly, Java, Pascal utilized in software development projects.
- Demonstrated a strong commitment to continuous learning, staying updated with emerging technologies and industry trends.

Skills: Python, Java, C/C++, Assembly

Education

Nazarbayev University - Astana, Kazakhstan - B.Sc

Mar 2015 – May 2019

GPA: 4.0/4.0

- Distributed Database Systems
- Cloud Computing
- Foundations of Algorithms